http://www.tournamentcable.com/privacy-policy

Menu
Search
Cart
Featured TackleLures & Rigging Supplies
Bomber CD-30'sCollapsible Spreader BarsDaisy ChainsDeep RunnersIlanderJoe ShutesLure SetsPlaners & BridlesRigging SuppliesSmart Bars/ TC's Premium Side-TrackersSplash BarsSpreader BarsSpreader/Splash Bar Rigging SuppliesSurface TeasersTeaser Baits
Boat & Cockpit Accessories
Anchor Retrieval & LineBelts & HarnessesBlock & TackleCooler MatsFish BagsFlagsHarpoonsOutrigger SuppliesSafety LinesTeaser Booms
Terminal Tackle
Bait Rigging SuppliesLure Rigging SuppliesHook Sets
Keel Weighted Double Hook SetsKeel Weighted Single Hook SetsStandard Double Hook SetsStandard Single Hook Sets
Hooks
Eagle ClawMustadQuickRig
Leader Material
CableFluorocarbonMonoWire
Premade Natural Bait Rigs
Double Hook RigsPremium Ballyhoo RigsStandard Ballyhoo Rigs
Sleeves & CrimpsSwivels & Snap Swivels
AFWQuickRig
WeightsWind-On Leaders & Top Shots
Tools
Bait Rigging SuppliesBench CrimpersCutters & PliersHand CrimpersHaywire Twist MachineRigging NeedlesSplicing Needles
Specific Species
Mahi/DolphinMarlinShark - Rigs & MoreStriped Bass - Rigs & MoreSwordfish/Deep Drop
Deep Drop Tackle
TunaWahoo
Dredge Teasers & Accessories
Center Console Dredges & AccessoriesDredges
Bucket DredgesEZ/6 Collapsible - BEST SELLER!Standard Fixed Dredges Ready to RigSlow TrollingTier-Drop Dredges
Dredge Accessories
Shackles, Swivels & SnapsReplacement ArmsPulleysWeights
Dredge Bait WiresDredge Teaser BaitsRods & ReelsTeaser BoomsTow LinesVertical Dead Boat
Palm Beach Teaser BarsRod, Reel & Line
Deep Drop RodsDredge RodsLP ReelsLine
Momoi
Planer RodsSafety Lines
What's Trending Near You
Northeast Coast
New YorkNew JerseyConnecticutMaineMassachusettsRhode Island
Mid-Atlantic Coast
AustraliaNew ZealandEurope
• At Tournament Cable Inc. we combine experience, innovation, and technology to produce the ultimate global sport-fishing tackle. •
Featured TackleLures & Rigging Supplies
Bomber CD-30'sCollapsible Spreader BarsDaisy ChainsDeep RunnersIlanderJoe ShutesLure SetsPlaners & BridlesRigging SuppliesSmart Bars/ TC's Premium Side-TrackersSplash BarsSpreader BarsSpreader/Splash Bar Rigging SuppliesSurface TeasersTeaser Baits
Boat & Cockpit Accessories
Anchor Retrieval & LineBelts & HarnessesBlock & TackleCooler MatsFish BagsFlagsHarpoonsOutrigger SuppliesSafety LinesTeaser Booms
Terminal Tackle
Bait Rigging SuppliesLure Rigging SuppliesHook Sets
Keel Weighted Double Hook SetsKeel Weighted Single Hook SetsStandard Double Hook SetsStandard Single Hook Sets
Hooks
Eagle ClawMustadQuickRig
Leader Material
CableFluorocarbonMonoWire
Premade Natural Bait Rigs
Double Hook RigsPremium Ballyhoo RigsStandard Ballyhoo Rigs
Sleeves & CrimpsSwivels & Snap Swivels
AFWQuickRig
WeightsWind-On Leaders & Top Shots
Tools
Bait Rigging SuppliesBench CrimpersCutters & PliersHand CrimpersHaywire Twist MachineRigging NeedlesSplicing Needles
Specific Species
Mahi/DolphinMarlinShark - Rigs & MoreStriped Bass - Rigs & MoreSwordfish/Deep Drop
Deep Drop Tackle
TunaWahoo
Dredge Teasers & Accessories
Center Console Dredges & AccessoriesDredges
Bucket DredgesEZ/6 Collapsible - BEST SELLER!Standard Fixed Dredges Ready to RigSlow TrollingTier-Drop Dredges
Dredge Accessories
Shackles, Swivels & SnapsReplacement ArmsPulleysWeights
Dredge Bait WiresDredge Teaser BaitsRods & ReelsTeaser BoomsTow LinesVertical Dead Boat
Palm Beach Teaser BarsRod, Reel & Line
Deep Drop RodsDredge RodsLP ReelsLine
Momoi
Planer RodsSafety Lines
What's Trending Near You
Northeast Coast
New YorkNew JerseyConnecticutMaineMassachusettsRhode Island
Mid-Atlantic Coast
AustraliaNew ZealandEurope
Tournament CableAbout UsArticles & BlogVideosFAQShopWhat's NewGift CertificatesMy AccountTrack OrderShipping & ReturnsSitemapCustomer ServiceContact Us800-979-FISH (3474)609-463-1313Privacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsVisit Our Store28 Indian Trail Road, Unit 102Burleigh, NJ 08210Monday-Friday: 8am-5pmSaturday: 8am-12pmClosed Sundays
privacy policy
Our Commitment to Privacy and SecurityTournament Cable respects the privacy of our customers and their personal information. Please be assured that none of the personally identifiable information you submit on the Site is shared with any third party except our credit card transaction processing service provider when you use your credit card to place an order. Tournament Cable, Inc. takes every precaution to protect our Site users. Users that submit sensitive information via the Site are guaranteed in our practice that the information is protected to the best of our ability. Unfortunately, Tournament Cable, Inc. can not guarantee the security of every transaction over the internet 100%, but we strive to do our best.If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy statement, please contact us by telephone at 1-800-979-FISH or by email. If you prefer to write your concerns, address them to: Tournament Cable, Inc., 28 Indian Trail Road, Unit 102, Cape May Court House, New Jersey 08210.By visiting the Site you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. By accepting the Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy or the Site Terms & Conditions, please do not use or access our Site.The content of any comments, suggestions, questions, information and feedback received by Tournament Cable, Inc. shall be deemed to be non-confidential. Any comments or materials sent to Tournament Cable, Inc. through this Site, including all feedback, questions, comments suggestions, questionnaires and the like, shall become the sole property of Tournament Cable, Inc. Tournament Cable, Inc. shall be free to use any such suggestions, comments, concepts and the like for any and all purposes of its sole choosing without payment of any compensation.Collection and Use of Personal InformationPersonal Identifiable InformationWhen you place a web order on the Site, we ask for your name, company name (if applicable), shipping address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, including your credit card number, billing address and CV code. As mentioned above, this information is processed by a third party merchant service provider, which is the only third party that has access to this information. Our service provider receives this information only for the purpose of processing your order, and is obligated to keep your information confidential. In addition, we ask for the name and address of the individual to whom you would like your order to be shipped, if other then yourself. When our e-commerce order requires a user to enter sensitive information, (i.e. credit card no., address, telephone number, etc.) that information is encrypted and is protected. Upon verification that your order has been fulfilled, Tournament Cable, Inc. does not retain or store any personal data.Email InquiriesWhen you email an inquiry to us, we receive your email address and any other information you choose to disclose in your email. The content of any email inquiries received by Tournament Cable, Inc. shall be deemed to be non-confidential. Any inquiries or materials sent to Tournament Cable, Inc. through this Site shall become the sole property of Tournament Cable, Inc. Tournament Cable, Inc. shall be free to use any such inquiries or material for any and all purpoes of its sole choosing, without payment of any compensation.Third Party Access to InformationProtection of Our Site and OthersTournament Cable, Inc. may disclose information you provide to our Site when we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law; to enforce or apply our Site Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or to protect the rights, privacy or safety of our Site, our users or others.Business TransfersInformation submitted to this Site is an asset of Tournament Cable, Inc. and will become part of our normal business records. If Tournament Cable, Inc. or a substantial part of our business is sold or otherwise transferred to a third party, such as a legal successor in interest, your information may be transferred to that third party.Legally Compelled Disclosure of InformationTournament Cable, Inc. may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights. A mere telephone requests will not be honored from any law enforcement agency without the appropriate documentation evidencing the authorization and the release of such information being requested.Updated September 13, 2005
If you aren't on our email list, you're missing out!
Stay current on all of the latest here at Tournament Cable. New products, discounts, sales, special announcements, and more!
800-979-FISH (3474)
AT TOURNAMENT CABLE INC. WE COMBINE EXPERIENCE, INNOVATION, AND TECHNOLOGY TO PRODUCE THE ULTIMATE GLOBAL SPORT-FISHING TACKLE.
© 1997-2018 TOURNAMENT CABLE INC.
Please wait
